This should be in two tables, patients and treatments.
这应该出现在患者和治疗两个表格中
Patients would be exactly the same in terms of these columns here.
对于这里的所有列而言 患者将完全相同
All 14 would remain.
所有 14 将保留
Then I'd argue that the adverse reaction column of the adverse reactions table,
我会认为不良反应表的不良反应列
the very last one down here,
就在这里 即 最后一列
I'd argue that this belongs in the treatments table.
我认为此列属于治疗表
If we want to look at treatment data,
如果我们想查看治疗数据
the adverse reaction for that treatment is naturally connected.
该治疗的不良反应是自然相关的
This is the same type of observational unit.
这是同一类型的观察单位
So because the other two columns in this adverse reactions table,
因为该不良反应表中的另外两列
given name and surname,
即名和姓
are actually duplicated in the treatments and also the patients table.
实际上在治疗表中是重复的 在患者表中也是如此
We'll actually also want to remove these duplicate column names.
实际上 我们也想删除这些重复的列名称
Duplicate column names can be found more generally in Pandas,
一般情况下使用下列代码
using these following code.
在 Pandas 中找到重复的列名称
This first line creates a list of all of
第一行创建了整个数据集 (即 三个表格) 中
the column names across the whole data set, all three tables worth.
所有列名称的列表
Puts it into a series.
将其放入一个系列中
Then we use the dot_duplicated method on
然后 我们将 dot_duplicated 方法运用到该系列上
that series and we see that given name and surname are duplicated.
发现名和姓重复
This list, then the data frame,
该列表 然后 DataFrame
returns a list of all of the columns in the data frame.
返回DataFrame中所有列的列表
So with these duplicate given name and surname columns removed,
删除这些重复的名和姓
as well as the other two tidiness issues fixed,
并解决其余两个整洁度问题
our final tidy data set should look like this.
我们最后得到的整洁数据集应该是这样
Two tables, patients, treatments,
两个表格 即 患者和治疗
with the only shared column between the two being patient ID.
两者之间唯一的共有列是患者 ID
It's best practice to have the ID as one primary identifier across tables,
最好的做法是将 ID 用作两个表格的一个主要标识符
because ID won't change. Name could change.
因为 ID 不会改变 姓名可能改变
For example, if someone legally changes their name via marriage or something.
例如 如果有人通过婚姻或其它事情依法变更了姓名
So having given name and surname in one table only,
名和姓仅在一个表格中出现
means you only have to update these columns in one table.
意味着你只需要在一个表格中更新这些列
Consolidating these three tables as they currently stand,
将现在分别表示为
patients, treatments, adverse reactions,
患者、治疗和不良反应
into the two displayed here,
的三个表格合并为这里所示的两个表格
requires joining, which is something you'll do in lesson four of this course.
这个需要进行联接 这是你将在第四课中要做的事情